Assistant Manager - JC Enterprise DE

I am qualified and professional with four years of experience in deals with a target market that stays in need of the products and I am flexible learner with Marketing Management Strong and analytical skills. Team player with an eye for detail.

yuvrajct@gmail.com

9600453235

Coimbatore, India

0

linkedin.com/in/yuvaraj-jaganathan-63022341



EDUCATION

B.Sc., Information Technology

Maharaja Arts & Science College

06/2008 - 06/2011

HSC

Govt Boys Higher Secondary School

03/2007 - 05/2008

SSI C

Govt Boys Higher Secondary School

06/2005 - 05/2006

WORK EXPERIENCE

Assistant Manager – JC Enterprise DE

Reliance SMSL Limited

10/2022 - Current

- Drive small and medium enterprise business in the assigned territory.
- Pitch enterprise products and services to
- prospective customers.
- Create sales funnel and ensure account
- penetration.

Assistant Sales Manager

Axis Bank Ltd

- Plans and implements sales and service strategies, particularly as it relates to business banking products and services
- Builds and maintains positive working relationships with other members of Business Banking department.
- Provides clerical and administrative support in achieving department goals.

EDP Assistant & System Admin

National Textile Corporation Ltd

09/2012 - 05/2016

- Networking Planning is also the responsibility of EDP Department
- Installing New System, Upgradation of systems in various department
- Securities like Antivirus, Internet Security and Firewall

QUALITY CONTROLLER

Merrill Technology India Pvt Ltd.

11/2011 - 06/2012

- Excellent knowledge in Proof Reading
- To Verify of the Document against Template
- Experienced in Funds Documents(Annual Report, Semi-Annual Report, Prospectus)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Networking: created a topology of WAN network for multiple cities and configured Router and Switch, OSPF, DHCP, after checking the connectivity configured ACL, VLAN, Telnet&SSH and PAT with using Ipv4.

AWS (Amazon Web Services): Build a Hosted DNS service for creating IAM, configured VPC, Subnets, NAT and webserver, created Load Balancer and Security Groups connected with EC2 Instances, using S3, implement Auto scaling group, enabled cloud watch and Route 53, installed RDS(SQL) and taking remote for private subnet from public subnet.

Linux: Break the root password and configured network management created a group with five users and assigned permissions and passwords for users, setting LVM and resized, SSH, crontab and swap configuration.

CERTIFICATES

- * Certified Cisco CCNA-I(N+) in KGiSL MicroCollege
- * Certified AWS(Amazon Web Services) in KGiSL MicroCollege
- * Certified RedHat Linux Administrator in KGiSL MicroCollege
- * Certified Hardware(A+) in Beta Technologies

LANGUAGES

English

Full Professional Proficiency

Kannada

Professional Working Proficiency

Tamil

Native or Bilingual Proficiency